<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&lt;blink&gt;blimey&lt;/blink&gt;</title>
    <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on &lt;blink&gt;blimey&lt;/blink&gt;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 13:08:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blinkingblimey.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-us-v-european-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 13:08:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-us-v-european-banking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Entirely my fault for not planning ahead, but am always taken by surprise at how slow US banking is. European transfers are complete before the confirmation page loads, in the US, well, maybe next week. Sometime. If you’re lucky.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-nearly-a-failed-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:03:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-nearly-a-failed-state/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The very idea of having doctors write prescriptions for money off energy bills is bizarre. That the Treasury are flying the kite in a national paper is madness. It all just adds to the idea that the UK is teetering on the brink of breakdown. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thesun.co.uk/money/19569772/doctors-money-prescription-energy-bills/&#34;&gt;DOC BILL HELP PLAN &lt;em&gt;The Sun&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-09-finally-a-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 18:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-09-finally-a-pi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can’t remember how long I’ve been trying to buy one. Now it’s here, I’m almost scared to open it.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://blinkingblimey.com/images/raspberrypi4initsbox.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;raspberrypi4initsbox&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-07-holiday-gestation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 22:44:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-07-holiday-gestation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently in the nesting phase of holiday gestation; tidying and organising everything to within an inch of its life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-12-21-mrna-vaccines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-12-21-mrna-vaccines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure exactly how an mRNA vaccine works, but having had my booster yesterday I spent most of today asleep or feeling awful. Then, since five, I’ve felt absolutely great.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A year without work</title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-11-04-year-without-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 18:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-11-04-year-without-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve now gone just over a year since I last ‘worked’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not quite sure how deliberate this has been. The preceding eighteen months saw a couple of disastrous career moves, but my last day of work arrived much sooner than I’d anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a month into a three-month notice period, I trekked into work as usual. I was feeling unusually tired, but thought little of it. Then Test and Trace rang to follow up on my positive Covid-19 test.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d taken the test a week before, a precaution after Covid-19 swept through my workplace. The hospital lab (I was working in the NHS) had reported a negative result, but I headed home to self-isolate to be safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was quickly apparent who was right, by the afternoon I had developed symptoms. Over the few days I experienced, except for the cough, almost every symptom that has been associated with the virus. I was fortunate, though, that I only had one night of breathing difficulties. I cannot imagine the fear experienced by those who needed hospitalisation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fatigue was the biggest problem. Three months later I was still asleep half the day and even moderate exercise would write off the next twenty-four hours. Even today, I feel the after-effects, although I attribute these more to my general loss of fitness over the first six months than the virus directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it put paid to my plans to find a new job. I’d started my hunt and had to turn down an interview and a few recruiters while I was self-isolating. I was, however, fortunate to have a supportive family and a bit of cash in the bank to tide me over. There was no immediate danger, but there was the challenge of finding a job when I spent a lot of my time asleep and lacked stamina.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it has turned out I didn’t need to find a job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point, I put myself on a freelancing site offering copywriting. I charged peanuts, my thinking was that earning a few quid was better than earning nothing. And, at least, it gave me something to put on the CV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I earned a few quid. My perfectionist agonising over every word meant my hourly rate was probably pennies. But one job led to another, and another, and another. I quickly became overwhelmed. So, I increased my rates to limit the demand. But then it happened again. And again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without really planning anything, I’ve got to a stage where I’m making ends meet. And that’s largely by working half-days with cheap rates. (Covid-19 has helped too. Our expenditure on restaurants and holidays is not what it was.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not sure what to make of all of this. Thinking back, I always enjoyed writing and, when the opportunity presented at work or elsewhere, relished the opportunity to play with words. But although I’d been paid for a few bits of writing, it was never something I imagined I could live on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even writing this, the imposter syndrome creeps in: who on earth would pay someone who writes dross like this? It’s simply laughable to compare myself with ‘real’ writers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my more confident moments, though, I think there are two things that stick out for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, I am incredibly fortunate to be in the position where I could do this. Few people could afford the risk of trying it, let alone stumbling into it as I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, doing something you genuinely enjoy, that you find rewarding, where the senses are satisfied (and how I love the rhythmic sounds and light touch of my keyboard), just does not feel like work. Flow comes easily. Pleasing phrases and passages present themselves. Pieces magically appear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have no idea what the future will hold. Perhaps I will tire of trying to pretend I’m a writer (or copywriter). Perhaps I will stumble across a job I cannot refuse. Perhaps someone will rumble me and everyone will find out this emperor is as naked as the day they were born. All I can do is enjoy it while it lasts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-10-23-happy-hours-on-a-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 18:21:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-10-23-happy-hours-on-a-bench/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The combination of ambiguous phrasing and anonymous initials makes me wonder what they did in those ‘happy hours’. (As well as making me very fond of Mrs Macfarlane.) &lt;img src=&#34;https://blinkingblimey.com/images/mrsmacfarlane.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mrs Macfarlene bench memorial&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-10-19-tinkering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 20:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-10-19-tinkering/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve just spent an age tinkering with Github Actions and Pages to automate building a Hugo site. Something I imagine many people would do in moments, but there&amp;rsquo;s a real sense joy in accomplishing even something that simple.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-28-recognition-at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-28-recognition-at-last/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a sporadic, and not very good, photographer, it’s nice to get a picture &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-humber-58718921&#34;&gt;used by the BBC for an article&lt;/a&gt;. Not a massive news story, and I think Grimsby has far bigger problems than the clock, but nice for the ego. &lt;img src=&#34;https://blinkingblimey.com/images/grimsbyminster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Grimsby Minster at night&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-23-a-buggy-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:43:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-23-a-buggy-mess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m coming to the conclusion that all there is to be found at the intersection of iOS and iPadOS 15 and iCloud is a horrible buggy mess.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-22-ios15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-22-ios15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Much as I am enjoying iOS 15 (despite the havoc Safari is playing with my muscle memory), I&amp;rsquo;m not quite so keen on the subtle changes that seem to have destroyed every single one of my tortuously complicated Shortcuts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-15-governmenttrolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-15-governmenttrolling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is it a government reshuffle, or is it just Johnson trolling a nation? Nadine Dorries? In the Cabinet? So hard to see how she&amp;rsquo;s better than, say, even the lamentable Williamson, who&amp;rsquo;s out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-literalclubcriticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-literalclubcriticism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a &lt;a href=&#34;https://literal.club&#34;&gt;Literal.club&lt;/a&gt; account, hoping a shiny new site would help me reboot my lapsed reading habit. I just wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready for the criticism. &lt;img src=&#34;https://blinkingblimey.com/images/literalcriticism.png&#34; alt=&#34;Literal.club&amp;rsquo;s hurtful criticism&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-applekeynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-applekeynote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My favourite thing about Apple keynotes is how, every year, they remind me that I could be a great photographer. I just need a marginally better camera in my pocket than I have carried for the past year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-12-cinema/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-12-cinema/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My first trip to the cinema since December 2019. I had quite forgotten how (once you are past the initial irritation) the reactive rustling of wrappers, murmurs, and throat-clearing add to the shared experience of movie watching!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging like it’s 2008</title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-08-blogginglikeits2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-08-blogginglikeits2008/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started tinkering with websites in the late 90s. Hand coding the HTML and learning cutting-edge techniques like frames and image maps to wring the potential out of Netscape Navigator. My first domain came in 2000, but it wasn’t until 2008 when I started blogging properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My blog is still technically alive — although I suspect that if I re-read it, I might experience life-threatening cringing — but for all practical purposes is died in the early 2010s. The posts were in a rut, and the drafts folder was full of snippets that were full of promise, but impaled on the spike of self-censorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The odd thing is that the early blogging was an incredibly positive experience for me. I learned a lot just through the work of maintaining and writing it. It resulted in meeting people I still know and keep in touch with, and even generated a good chunk of work, some of it for organisations I’m still involved with. There was a frisson of excitement attached to blogging, and I was suddenly nostalgic for it when doom-scrolling Twitter one day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was always a dopamine hit with Twitter. I was a fairly early adopter of it, before I started blogging, and remember being at an unconference (which I was involved in through blogging) talking to someone else about our excitement at both passing 100 followers. And we were both following everyone back because it was about conversation and discovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now the dopamine hit comes from broadcasting your fixed opinions, reading things you agree with while blocking or muting people you think are idiots. It has long since ceased to be a venue for healthy debate or discourse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, this is an attempt to return to 2008. If nothing else, I had fun setting up Hugo and GitHub Pages, ticking the wannabe geek box. It’s a bit out of the way of my main site, using a domain which, for some reason, I bought years ago. The distance will hopefully stop the self-censorship. And it’s deliberately disconnected from things like Twitter, connected only to micro-blog, which, I think, has more of an early Twitter vibe to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It might all stutter and fade after this post, but at least I’ll have given it a go. If I’m going to stop having a personal internet presence, I want to dump it saying “it wasn’t me, it’s you.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-05-helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-05-helloworld/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Having spent a chunk of time this weekend tinkering with a new blog I suppose I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to put some content on the damn thing. Cue loss of inspiration, followed by crippling self-censorship.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
