<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on &lt;blink&gt;blimey&lt;/blink&gt;</title>
    <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on &lt;blink&gt;blimey&lt;/blink&gt;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:18:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My mother, the pessimist</title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-09-06-my-mother-the-pessimist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:18:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-09-06-my-mother-the-pessimist/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps all children are cursed and, eventually, become their parents. And so, I find myself, increasingly, adopting views and traits that I recognise as theirs.
One I have become very aware of is my mother’s pessimism. It wasn’t a mild pessimism, the glum prediction of rain on a sunny day, but a doom-laden vision of the future.
Whenever the news contained stories of another nation’s despair — the death tolls of famines, the disease-ridden refugee camps of civil war — she would see our future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-us-v-european-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 13:08:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-us-v-european-banking/</guid>
      <description>Entirely my fault for not planning ahead, but am always taken by surprise at how slow US banking is. European transfers are complete before the confirmation page loads, in the US, well, maybe next week. Sometime. If you’re lucky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-nearly-a-failed-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:03:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-21-nearly-a-failed-state/</guid>
      <description>The very idea of having doctors write prescriptions for money off energy bills is bizarre. That the Treasury are flying the kite in a national paper is madness. It all just adds to the idea that the UK is teetering on the brink of breakdown. DOC BILL HELP PLAN The Sun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-09-finally-a-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 18:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-09-finally-a-pi/</guid>
      <description>I can’t remember how long I’ve been trying to buy one. Now it’s here, I’m almost scared to open it. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-07-holiday-gestation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 22:44:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/22-08-07-holiday-gestation/</guid>
      <description>Currently in the nesting phase of holiday gestation; tidying and organising everything to within an inch of its life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-12-21-mrna-vaccines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-12-21-mrna-vaccines/</guid>
      <description>I’m not sure exactly how an mRNA vaccine works, but having had my booster yesterday I spent most of today asleep or feeling awful. Then, since five, I’ve felt absolutely great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A year without work</title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-11-04-year-without-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 18:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-11-04-year-without-work/</guid>
      <description>I’ve now gone just over a year since I last ‘worked’.
I’m not quite sure how deliberate this has been. The preceding eighteen months saw a couple of disastrous career moves, but my last day of work arrived much sooner than I’d anticipated.
About a month into a three-month notice period, I trekked into work as usual. I was feeling unusually tired, but thought little of it. Then Test and Trace rang to follow up on my positive Covid-19 test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-10-23-happy-hours-on-a-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 18:21:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-10-23-happy-hours-on-a-bench/</guid>
      <description>The combination of ambiguous phrasing and anonymous initials makes me wonder what they did in those ‘happy hours’. (As well as making me very fond of Mrs Macfarlane.) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-10-19-tinkering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 20:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-10-19-tinkering/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just spent an age tinkering with Github Actions and Pages to automate building a Hugo site. Something I imagine many people would do in moments, but there&amp;rsquo;s a real sense joy in accomplishing even something that simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-28-recognition-at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-28-recognition-at-last/</guid>
      <description>As a sporadic, and not very good, photographer, it’s nice to get a picture used by the BBC for an article. Not a massive news story, and I think Grimsby has far bigger problems than the clock, but nice for the ego. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-23-a-buggy-mess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:43:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/2021-09-23-a-buggy-mess/</guid>
      <description>I’m coming to the conclusion that all there is to be found at the intersection of iOS and iPadOS 15 and iCloud is a horrible buggy mess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-22-ios15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-22-ios15/</guid>
      <description>Much as I am enjoying iOS 15 (despite the havoc Safari is playing with my muscle memory), I&amp;rsquo;m not quite so keen on the subtle changes that seem to have destroyed every single one of my tortuously complicated Shortcuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-15-governmenttrolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-15-governmenttrolling/</guid>
      <description>Is it a government reshuffle, or is it just Johnson trolling a nation? Nadine Dorries? In the Cabinet? So hard to see how she&amp;rsquo;s better than, say, even the lamentable Williamson, who&amp;rsquo;s out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-literalclubcriticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-literalclubcriticism/</guid>
      <description>Got a Literal.club account, hoping a shiny new site would help me reboot my lapsed reading habit. I just wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready for the criticism. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-applekeynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-14-applekeynote/</guid>
      <description>My favourite thing about Apple keynotes is how, every year, they remind me that I could be a great photographer. I just need a marginally better camera in my pocket than I have carried for the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-12-cinema/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-12-cinema/</guid>
      <description>My first trip to the cinema since December 2019. I had quite forgotten how (once you are past the initial irritation) the reactive rustling of wrappers, murmurs, and throat-clearing add to the shared experience of movie watching!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging like it’s 2008</title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-08-blogginglikeits2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-08-blogginglikeits2008/</guid>
      <description>I started tinkering with websites in the late 90s. Hand coding the HTML and learning cutting-edge techniques like frames and image maps to wring the potential out of Netscape Navigator. My first domain came in 2000, but it wasn’t until 2008 when I started blogging properly.
My blog is still technically alive — although I suspect that if I re-read it, I might experience life-threatening cringing — but for all practical purposes is died in the early 2010s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-05-helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blinkingblimey.com/posts/21-09-05-helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Having spent a chunk of time this weekend tinkering with a new blog I suppose I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to put some content on the damn thing. Cue loss of inspiration, followed by crippling self-censorship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
